iguides.org 2015-06-08

# Internet Guide - Web Directory- Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to iGuides.This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that iGuides collects, and the ways in which iGuides uses that personal information.

NB: iGuides will never sell your personal information, including your email address, to a 3rd party. 3rd party information sharing will be done strictly in accordance with the information disclosed below.

### Personal information use and collection: overview

iGuides reserves the right to collect and use personal information such as the following:

  * Information concerning your personal use of this website (i.e.: whether it is for a sole proprietor, a business or personal use, etc.)
  * personal data that you provide to register with the website
  * Information relating to transactions carried out over this website
  * Information provided by you that is necessary for subscribing to the website services (including credit card details, if applicable). Note: all credit card transactions are done via standard secure methods. You will never be asked for credit card details or any other financial details by email. If iGuides requires financial details, we will direct you to our secure servers

### iGuides' use of your personal information

iGuides may make use of your personal information to: 

  * Administer this website
  * Personalize your entries for you (subject to your permission)
  * Enable you to access and use these website services 
  * Publish certain information about you on our website (subject to your permission)
  * Deliver products to you that you purchase, if applicable
  * Provide you with services 
  * Email your statements and invoices
  * Take authorized payments from you
  * Email you marketing material (subject to your permission)

Personal information disclosed to iGuides’ agents or subcontractors for the above purposes will be subject to the same terms of this iGuides privacy statement. 

iGuides may also disclose your personal information as required by law in connection with prospective or actual legal proceedings and/or in order to exercise or defend iGuides’ legal rights or to establish verification of those rights. 

### Data Security

iGuides will take all reasonable precautions in order to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

Your personal information will be stored on iGuides’ secure servers and secure back-up systems. 

iGuides will protect all information concerning electronic transactions with encryption technology.

### International data transfers

Information collected by iGuides may be stored and/or processed in any country where iGuides has operations. This information will be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

Personal information that you submit to iGuides for publication will be published on the internet and available throughout the world. Acceptance of any of iGuides’ services is tantamount to your agreement to international transfers of personal information. 

### Updating this statement

iGuides may occasionally update this privacy policy. You are advised to check this page regularly to ensure that you aware of any changes. 

### Other websites

The iGuides directory contains links to many other websites. iGuides bears no responsibility for the privacy policies of any third parties.

### Contact iGuides

If you have any questions about the iGuides privacy policy or iGuides’ use of your personal information, please contact us

By email: [EMAIL ADDRESS]
